right after I started the IVs back in December
was that all was I mean my brain was it it it
it it I I I felt like it was clearer
like it was like thoughts came very easy
I didn't have to search for words
I didn't have to search for names
I didn't have to search for different things
and go what was that what was that
I just it's amazing how clear after I
got the ivdmso my brain was again
after we got done with the exam
he he he looked at me
and he um he sat down with me
and after the exam
and he goes  look
I would never tell somebody this on their first visit
I think you have a motor neuron issue
and um and I think it's ALS
and especially last winter
um I started going downhill and started
having a lot of breathing issues  um I was
uh it would happen during the day
but the worst was at night
where I would find that um
my uh breathing in the middle of the night
I'd wake up 5
10 times a night
it seemed like um
in a complete panic as though I was drowning
as if my diaphragm had just stopped
and wasn't moving my lungs anymore
and at times I'd have to force myself
to exhale before I could inhale
last winter I thought I was
actually on the way downhill
in fact we actually ordered a wheelchair
do you ever use DMSO intravenously on an animal
and uh she said yes  uh I do
and I said well when would you do that
and she said well if I had an animal
that was down and couldn't get up
um  and it had a severe neurological problem
and I stopped it right there and I go
severe neurological problem
and can't get up
I said that sounds an awful lot like ALS
and she says yeah
kind of does
I said well
I said so you give it intervinously
I said does it work
and she goes yeah
many times it does
many times I can get the horse up on its feet
or the animal
I can get it on its feet and start working with it
and start treating it  and I said  well
that's amazing  I said
so we're using that for a severe neurological
problem on an animal that can't get up
but we're not doing this for humans
and she said yeah
so I thought well
let's try putting the DMSO on my spine
let's see if my spinal issues could
have something to do with with this
and the thing that I found that was amazing
was that within three days of doing that  those
uh  episodes of waking up like I was
drowning completely stopped
I started sleeping better
I started feeling better
I started getting strength back in my arms
I actually was able to pull the
trusses across the road  you know
so 30 feet across the road
to where the the the crane could pick him up
and each of those trusses weighed 340 pounds
and I I told my wife that that night I'm like
I can't believe it's the first time in years that
I felt my muscles work correctly in my arms
it showed that I had gone from spending
90% of the night with my oxygen levels at
89 or below to only 42% of the night
and my longest episode had gone from
13 minutes down to four minutes
and the number of episodes had greatly decreased
I stopped using the DMSO on October 31st
I didn't tell my wife
I didn't tell anybody what I was doing
the weakness in the legs and the
arms started coming back
I I s I noticed uh I was my endurance was dropping off
um  I I had I I just I had no energy
my wife um she came up and asked me
and she said she said Todd
it doesn't seem like the the DMSO's working  and um
she goes you you you're not doing well
I don't understand what happened within
that first 24 hours after using the DMSO
I was amazed at how much better I was feeling
and then over the next week things just started it
kept getting better and better and better
for the past 10 years
one of the things that I I I I noticed when all
this all started was the issues with my legs
they felt like wet noodles
they felt like they didn't have strength
and I I I called it my jelly legs
even applying the topical DMSO
I never got rid of the jelly legs  I mean
there was improvements
but I never got rid of it
um but with the IV DMSO it went away
they felt stronger than they'd felt in 10 years
and I sat down on his table and I said DOC
check my reflexes
he just looked at me and goes OK
he walked over
and he checked the reflex at my
right knee and it barely moved
it hasn't done that in years
and he looked at me and he goes Todd
that was almost normal
I cannot describe enough the difference
between the way I was yesterday morning
before I went and got the IV
and then yesterday evening
and then even today  um
in how how much clearer
and articulate my brain is  um
it's it's it's amazing to me
and and and literally how much better I feel
how much better I can talk
how much better I can breathe
especially the breathing